// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the tallest bulding in the world?",
    answer: "Burj Khalifa",
    options: [
      "Emirates Tower",
      "Burj Khalifa",
      "Lotus Tower",
      "WTC"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which building has the unique feature of 7850 stars that filter sunlight into the museum?",
    answer: "Louvre Abu Dhabi",
    options: [
      "Louvre Paris",
      "Louvre Abu Dhabi",
      "Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque",
      "Masjidun Noor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is a planned city that aims to be zero-carbon and zero-waste, and the Dubai Sustainable City, which is a residential community that runs entirely on solar power and has a green central courtyard?",
    answer: "Masdar City in Abu Dhabi",
    options: [
      "Sharjah",
      "Fujairah",
      "Masdar City in Abu Dhabi",
      "Ras Al Khaimah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is a natural island located off the coast of Abu Dhabi in the United Arab Emirates?",
    answer: "Sir Bani Yas Island",
    options: [
      "Palm Jumeirah",
      "Bluewaters Island",
      "Jumeirah Bay Island",
      "Sir Bani Yas Island"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the man-made lake that sits at its center? The tranquil waters of the lake are surrounded by a pristine sandy beach",
    answer: "Qudra Oasis",
    options: [
      "Qudra Oasis",
      "Hatta Lake",
      "Al Mamzar Lake",
      "Burj Khalifa Lake"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the dish cooked with aromatic spices, while the meat is marinated in a blend of spices and then cooked with onions and tomatoes. Vegetables such as carrots, peas, and tomatoes are often added for added flavor and nutrition. It is served with a side of yogurt or a spicy tomato sauce, as well as salad or pickles.",
    answer: "Machboos",
    options: [
      "Khubz",
      "Machboos",
      "Chebab",
      "Mandi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What features a 10 million-liter tank that houses thousands of marine animals, a 48-meter-long underwater tunnel, a Glass Bottom Boat ride, interactive experiences such as the Shark Encounter and the Underwater Zoo, and state-of-the-art facilities and interactive experiences.",
    answer: "Dubai Aquarium",
    options: [
      "Burj Khalifa",
      "Ferrari World",
      "Dubai Aquarium",
      "Palm Jumeirah"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the most unique and iconic architectural landmarks in dubai?",
    answer: "Palm Jumeirah",
    options: [
      "Dubai Mall",
      "Palm Jumeirah",
      "Burj Al Arab",
      "The Dubai Fountain"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is a popular street food in Dubai and what is it made of?",
    answer: "Shawarma",
    options: [
      "Shawarma",
      "Burger",
      "Chebab",
      "Kebab"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 10,
    question: "When does dubai food festival take place?",
    answer: "February or March",
    options: [
      "April or May",
      "September or October",
      "February or March",
      "January or February"
    ]
  },
];

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
// ];